我还有一年活头了 萨姆
I got a year to live, Sam.
我想好好利用
I'd like to make the most of it.
怎么样 我们一起去杀些凶鬼恶灵
So, what do you say we kill some evil sons of bitches.
惹点麻烦吧
And we raise a little hell?
（忆往昔）
你没告诉迪恩吗
You didn't tell Dean?
告诉我什么
Tell me what?
来了个新红人
There's a big new up-and-comer.
她叫莉莉丝
Her name is Lilith.
她真的很想把萨姆的内脏插在棍子上
And she really, really wants Sam's intestines on a stick.
马上解除迪恩的交易
Let Dean out of his deal right now.
我只是推销的
I'm just a saleswoman.
我也像其他人一样有老板
I got a boss like everybody.
合同在谁手里
Who holds the contract?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
她真名叫贝拉·塔伯特
Bela Talbot's her real name.
柯尔特枪
The Colt.
贝拉偷了柯尔特枪
Bela stole the Colt.
我要拿回它 贝拉
I want it back, Bela.
那把小手枪吗
You little pistol, you mean?
抱歉
Sorry.
你知道你这么做会害死多少人吗
You understand how many people are gonna die if you do this?
你究竟以为我打算拿它做什么
What exactly is it that you think I plan to do with it?
拿走我们对付恶魔大军的唯一武器
Take the only weapon we have against an army of demons.
卖给出价最高者
and sell it to the highest bidder?
你对我一无所知
You know nothing about me.
收拾东西
Pack your crap.
干吗 我们去哪
Why? Where we going?
我们要去找到那贱人
We're gonna go hunt the bitch down.
我不想下地狱
I don't wanna go to hell.
我们会想办法救你的
We'll find a way to save you.
我好怕 萨姆
I'm scared, Sam.
我真的好怕
I'm really scared.
唯一能帮我脱身的就是我自己
And the only person that can get me out of this thing is me.
还有我
And me.
（如今）
（宾夕法尼亚州 伊利）
- 喝酒去吗 - 去不了
- Up for a drink? - No, I can't.
我天一亮就得起床 有工作
I gotta be up at the crack of dawn. Duty calls.
- 隆胸吗 - 那还好了
- A boob job? - I wish.
不 有个坏脾气老太婆想整整
No, some crabby old broad wants the works.
我需要把叉子才能把她都支棱起来
I need a forklift to get it all back up.
麻烦那么一通 就为了给脸减龄15分钟吗
All that work to hack, what, 15 minutes off their faces?
保持年轻是桩残酷的生意
Staying young is a brutal business.
救命
Help!
放我出去
Let me out of here.
救命
Help!
先生
Sir?
求你
Please.
没事 先生 让我看看发生了什么
It's okay, sir. Let me see what happened.
别担心 我没什么没见过的
Don't you worry. There's nothing I haven't seen.
- 不不 - 让我看看
- No, no, no. - Let me see.
[邪恶力量 第3季第15集]
停下
Stop.
你愿开口了吗
You ready to talk?
我不知道
I don't know.
我什么都不知道
I don't know anything.
听到了吗 萨姆 他什么都不知道呢
You hear that, Sam? He doesn't know anything.
我听到了
Yeah, I heard.
我说的是实话
I'm telling you the truth.
是吗
You are?
天啊 那我该向你道歉
My God, then I owe you an apology.
我来弥补你一下吧
Allow me to make it up to you.
我再最后问你一次
I'm gonna ask you one last time.
我的合同在谁手里
Who holds my contract?
你妈妈
Your mother.
我把她弯下身前 她拿给我看了
Yeah, she, uh, showed it to me right before I bent her over.
我要个名字
I want a name.
- 否则 - 什么
- Or else… - Or what?
你还要把圣水从另一头挤进来吗
You gonna squirt your holy water in both ends?
得了
Please.
哥们 那算什么
Brother, that's like a flea bite,
我要是告诉你什么之后只会更惨
compared to what's coming to me if I tell you jack.
你尽管来吧
Do what you want.
我唯一怕的就是握着你小命的恶魔
The only thing I'm scared of is the demon holding your ticket.
感觉怎么样 感觉好吗
How's that feel? Does that feel good?
来吧
Go ahead.
送我回地狱吧
Send me back to hell.
因为等你到了那里 我会等着你
Because when you get there, I'll be waiting for you.
跟几个很期待
With a few pals who are dying for.
好好会会迪恩·温彻斯特的朋友一起迎你
a nice little meet and greet with Dean Winchester.
要我做吗
Should I?
送他去再伤害不了其他人的地方吧
Send him someplace he can't hurt anyone else.
你查了那指纹两次吗
You ran the prints twice?
你确定吗
You're sure?
好的
Okay. Yeah,
就说是实验室失误吧
just chalk it up to lab error.
可不是嘛 好
Don't I know it. Okay,
谢谢 我会转告警督
thanks. Yeah, I'll tell the lieutenant.
尸体埋了吗
Bury the body?
是啊 可怜人
Yeah. Poor schmuck.
这些恶魔似乎为了寻刺激狠狠地糟蹋了他的身体
It's like these demons ride him hard just for kicks.
那通电话怎么回事
What's the phone call about?
记得昨天报纸上那宗报道吗
Remember that thing in the paper yesterday?
脱衣舞娘用丁字裤闷死男子吗
Stripper suffocates dude with thighs?
另一件事
The other thing.
哦 那个走进急诊室
Right, the guy that walks into the ER.
立刻死亡 肠子掉出来的家伙
and kneels over dead, his stomach ripped out?
其实是他的肝脏
His liver, actually.
反正 我刚得知了些很有趣的事
Anyways, I just found out something pretty damn interesting.
什么事
What?
那具尸体
The dead body?
上面满是血指纹 但不属于被害人
Covered in bloody fingerprints. Not the victim's.
好 我《犯罪现场调查组》的哥们戴维·克鲁索
Okay. Great, my man Dave Caruso'll be.
听了肯定高兴
stoked to hear it.
指纹匹配一个死于1981年的男人
Those fingerprints match a guy who died in 1981.
是吗
Really?
那什么情况
So, what are we talking?
行尸吗
Walking dead?
- 杀人行尸吗 - 可能吧
- Walking, killing dead? - Maybe.
僵尸们的确喜欢另一种「另类白肉」
Zombies do like the other "other white meat."
说起来 你为什么在乎僵尸
Speaking of, what do you care about zombies?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你几个月来一直忙于拯救灵魂
What? You've been on soul-saving detail for months now,
我们只剩三周了
we're three weeks out.
你却突然想去灭僵尸了
and all of a sudden you're interested in some hot zombie action?
哥们 是你一心想去猎魔
Man, you're the one who's been all gung ho to hunt.
我以为你会喜欢呢
I just thought I'd be doing you a favor.
不不
No, no, no.
我没说我不想去
I didn't say I didn't wanna do it, okay?
不用说
I mean, obviously,
我很想去猎僵尸
I wanna hunt some zombies.
好啊 那好吧
Okay, fine. Whatever.
嗯 身体剩余部分没有被动过
Yup, the rest of the body was intact.
肝脏是唯一缺失的器官
The liver was the only organ missing.
肝脏被扯出的地方
Now, where the liver was ripped out,
你是否发现有牙印
did you happen to notice any teeth marks?
可以出示下你们的警徽吗
Can I see your badges?
当然
Of course, sure.
好吧 你们是警察还是白痴
Fine, so you're cops and morons.
什么 不 我们很聪明的
Excuse me? No, no, we're very smart.
肝脏不是扯出来的
The liver was not ripped out.
是用手术手法切除的
It was removed. Surgically.
此人很会使用手术刀
By someone who knew their way around a scalpel.
你们没读我的报告吗
Didn't you read my report?
当然读了
Of course we did.
引人入胜
It was, uh, riveting.
精彩纷呈 爱不释卷
It's a real page-turner. Just delightful.
你们没事了吧
You done?
应该没了
I think so.
请走吧
Please, go away.
好
Okay.
好的
Sure.
怎么了
What?
没什么
Nothing.
这下我们的僵尸理论是站不住了
So that kinda punches a hole in our zombie theory,
手术刀什么的
that scalpel thing?
嗯 会技术的僵尸 《僵尸女医生》
Yeah. Zombie with skills? Dr. Quinn, medicine zombie.
或许我们查错了方向 迪恩
Maybe we're on the wrong track, Dean,
不该找被切过的尸体
looking for hacked-up corpses.
那我们该找什么
What should we be looking for?
幸存者
Survivors.
这不是僵尸午餐 而是器官盗窃
This isn't zombie lunch. This is organ theft.
我昨天都跟警察说过了
I told the cops all of this yesterday.
我不想再谈了
I don't wanna talk about it anymore.
就问几个问题 先生
Just a couple questions, sir.
哥们 我刚被人盗了肾
Man, I just got my kidney stolen.
我累了
I'm tired.
我们很快就走
We'll be out of here quick.
你难道不想抓到那人吗
I mean, don't you wanna get the guy?
我的肾脏能回来吗
Will it get me back my kidney?
先生 你最后记得的事是什么
Sir, what's the last thing you remember?
给停车表投币
Feeding my meter.
我被从后面偷袭
I'm jumped from behind.
然后我醒来时 就被绑在了张台子上
and then I wake up strapped to a table.
然后是超乎你想象的剧痛
And then the worst pain you could possibly imagine, only worse.
然后我又昏了过去 谢天谢地
And then I black out again, thank God.
然后我在个小旅馆里尖叫着醒来
And then I wake up screaming in some no-tell motel,
躺在一浴缸冰水里
in a bathtub full of ice.
你记得手术的什么细节吗
Do you remember anything about the surgery?
那人的样貌 房间的具体情况
I mean, what the guy looked like, any details about the room?
我想想
Now, let me think about that.
嗯
Yeah.
我回忆起来一件事了 知道我记得什么吗
One thing is coming back to me. You know what I remember?
我的肾脏被切掉
Getting my kidney cut out of my body.
（19世纪医疗）
- 我有个理论 - 是吗
- So I got a theory. - Yeah?
嗯 我跟那位暴躁先生的医生谈过了
Yeah. I talked to Mr. Giggles' doctor.
原来 他的切口是用丝线缝合的
Turns out, his incisions were sewn up with silk.
- 奇怪啊 - 嗯
- That's weird. - Yeah,
现如今是奇怪
nowadays it is.
但在19世纪初 丝线可是
But silk used to be the suture of choice.
首选缝合线
back in early 19th century.
当时问题很大 病人会严重感染
It was problematic. Patients would get massive infections.
死亡率非常高
The death rate was insane.
- 好时代啊 - 嗯
- Good times. - Right.
所以医生们得尽全力
So doctors they had to do whatever they could.
避免感染的扩散
to keep infections from spreading.
一种办法就是用蛆
One way was maggots.
哥们 我吃饭呢
Dude, I'm eating.
而且效果很好
It actually kinda worked.
因为蛆只吃坏组织 而不碰好组织
because maggots, they eat bad tissue and they leave good tissue.
而且 那人被发现时
Now, get this, when they found our guy,
他体内塞满了蛆虫
his body cavity was stuffed full of maggots.
哥们 我吃饭呢
Dude, I'm eating.
好 是这样吗
All right, let me get this straight.
- 有人在被劫持 - 对
- So people are getting ganked, right? - Yeah.
古董巡回手术窃取器官
A little Antiques Roadshow surgery, some, some organ theft.
怎么听上去那么耳熟
Why is this all sounding familiar?
因为你听说过
Because you heard it before.
在你还小时
When you were a kid.
爸爸说过
From Dad.
班顿医生
Doc Benton.
曾生活在新罕布什尔的真医生 很天才
Real-life doctor, lived in New Hampshire, brilliant.
痴迷于炼金术 尤其是永生之法
And obsessed with alchemy, especially how to live forever.
1816年 医生抛下了他的诊所
So in 1816, Doc abandons his practice…
是 之后20年都没人有他的消息
Right, yeah, nobody hears from him for like 20 years.
然后突然开始有人死亡
All of a sudden people start showing up dead.
死亡 或丢失器官 或手 或其他身体部分
Dead or missing an organ, or a hand, or some other kind of part.
因为他不管做了什么 真的成功了
Cause whatever he was doing was actually working.
他的生命不断延续
He just kept on ticking.
器官用坏 他就拿新的换上
Parts would wear out, he'd replace them.
爸爸不是猎到了他 挖出了他的心脏吗
I thought Dad hunted him down and took his heart out.
是啊 医生肯定是按上了新的
Yeah, I guess the doc must've plugged in a new one.
好吧 他在哪干坏事呢
All right, where's he doing the deed?
这上面说 班顿对实验室的选址很挑剔
According to this, Benton's picky about where he sets up his lab.
他喜欢浓密的森林
He likes dense forest…
靠近河水或溪流 某种活水的地方
with access to a river or stream or some kind of fresh water.
为什么
Why?
因为他喜欢在那里丢弃
Because that's where he likes to dump the.
内脏和粪便
bile, and intestines, and fecal matter.
没胃口了吗
Lost your appetite yet?
宝贝 我才没法生你气呢
Baby, I can't stay mad at you.
不 求你
No, please.
不要
No, no.
不
No.
（伊利旅馆）
这都是旧狩猎小屋
So these are all old hunting cabins.
大都废弃多年了
They've mostly been abandoned for years.
那我们还等什么
Then what the hell are we waiting for?
鲍比
Bobby?
我可能总算有贝拉的线索了
I think I finally got a beat on Bela.
说
I'm listening.
鲁弗斯·特纳
Rufus Turner.
那是种性姿势吗
Is that like a Cleveland Steamer?
他是个猎人 至少以前是
He's a hunter, or used to be.
现在呢
And now?
基本上是个隐士 也卖东西作为副业
Hermit, mostly. Does a little selling on the side.
总之 我几个月前发话出去打听贝拉的消息
Anyway, I put the word out on Bela months ago.
他刚来电了 说有个女人联系他
He just called, said a woman got in touch,
想买点东西
wanted to buy some things.
- 他觉得是贝拉吗 - 英国口音
- And he thinks it's Bela? - British accent.
用了米娜·钱德勒这个名字
Went by the name Mina Chandler.
这名字她用过
She's used that before.
这挺大意啊
Well, that's kind of a sloppy move, isn't it,
联系你的一个老朋友
getting in contact with one of your old friends?
朋友 我们15年没见了
Friend? Haven't laid eyes on him in 15 years.
他也不会寄圣诞贺卡
And he's not the Christmas-card type.
她恐怕不知道我认识他
I doubt she knows I know him.
佛蒙特州 迦南
Canaan, Vermont.
谢谢 鲍比 我们就去
Thanks, Bobby, we're on our way.
还有件事
One other thing.
带一瓶尊尼获加蓝牌威士忌去
Take a bottle of Johnnie Walker Blue.
好
Okay.
走吧 我们去找贝拉
Come on. We're going after Bela.
什么
What?
- 等等 - 走吧
- Hold on a second… - Come on.
拿东西 时间不等人
Get your stuff, the clock's ticking.
我觉得我们该留下 查完案子
Look, I think we should stay here and finish the case.
你疯了吗
You insane?
迪恩 她不可能还留着柯尔特枪
Dean, there's no way she still has the Colt.
那是几个月前了 她八成刚拿到就卖出去了
That was months ago. She probably sold it the second she got it.
那我就杀了她 双赢
Well, then I'll kill her. Win-win.
- 迪恩 - 萨姆 我们走
- Dean… - Sam, we're going.
不
No.
为什么不
Why the hell not?
迪恩 这个案子
Dean, this, this here, now.
这能救你
This is what's gonna save you.
什么 找个弗兰肯斯坦吗
What? Chasing some Frankenstein?
是永生
Chasing immortality.
班顿死不了
Look, Benton can't die.
我们查明他怎么做到的 就能让你也那么做
We find out how he did it, we can do it to you.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你得先死然后才会下地狱 是吧
You have to die before you go to hell, right?
- 如果你死不了 - 等等 等一下
- So if you can never die… - Wait, wait, wait. Wait a second.
你是从一开始就知道这是班顿医生吗
Did you know that this was Doc Benton from the jump?
不
No.
- 我是希望 - 所以僵尸什么的
- Look, I was hoping… - So the whole zombie thing,
是骗我的吗
it was lying to me?
我没确定之前不想说什么 迪恩
I don't wanna say anything until I was sure, Dean.
我只是想找到个答案
All I'm trying to do is find an answer here.
不 你是在找一个把人切开的混蛋
No, what you're trying to do is chase Slicey McHackey here.
是为了杀他吗 不 你想请他喝啤酒
And to kill him? No, you wanna buy him a freaking beer.
你想研究他
You wanna study him.
我只是想帮你
I was just trying to help.
你不是在帮忙
You're not helping.
你忘了 如果我想钻空子 你会死
You forget that if I welch on this deal, you die.
知道吗 永生就是钻空子
Guess what? Living forever is welching.
好啊 那不管有什么魔药 我也服下
Fine, then whatever the magic pill is, I'll take it, too.
这算什么 《席德与南茜》吗
What is this, Sid and Nancy?
不 就像鲍比一直说的
No, it's just like Bobby's been saying.
我们杀了手握合同的恶魔
We kill the demon that holds the contract,
整件事就都打消了
this whole damn thing wipes clean.
那是最佳机会
That's our best shot.
即便你拿到了柯尔特枪 迪恩 你要冲谁开枪
Even if you had the Colt, Dean, who you gonna shoot?
我们不知道合同在谁那里
We have no idea who holds the ticket.
那我就在地狱之犬咬碎我前打死它们
I'll shoot the Hellhounds then, before they slash me up.
你来不来
Now, you coming or not?
我要留下
I'm staying here.
不 不行
No, you're not.
因为我不能允许你一个人进入森林
Cause, I'm not gonna let you wander out in the woods alone.
追踪一个偷器官的变态
to track some organ-stealing freak.
你不允许我吗
You're not gonna let me?
没错 我不允许
No, I'm not gonna let you.
你打算怎么阻止我
How are you gonna stop me?
听着 我们的目标是一致的
Look, man, we're trying to do the same thing here.
我知道
I know.
但我要走了
But I'm going.
所以如果你要留下 留下吧
So if you wanna stay, stay.
萨姆 多小心
Sammy, be careful.
你也是
You too.
（佛蒙特州 迦南）
（律师禁入 说你呢 别来要捐款 别来兜售东西）
干什么
What?
鲁弗斯
Rufus.
即便我是 问题不变 干什么
Yeah, even if I am, the question is still the same. What?
我是迪恩·温彻斯特 鲍比·辛格的朋友
I'm Dean Winchester, I'm a friend of Bobby Singer's.
那又如何
So?
你今早给他打过电话
You called him this morning.
那又如何
So?
你跟鲍比说
You told Bobby.
有个英国妞联系过你
about a British chick, made contact with you.
是啊 那又如何
Yeah, and so?
知道她在哪吗
Do you know where she is?
嗯
Yeah.
好啊 可以告诉我吗
Great. Could you tell me where I could find her?
不可以
No.
当然了
Of course not.
听着 鲁弗斯 伙计
Look, Rufus, man…
我跟你说明白了
Look, let me point something out to you.
是你来敲我的门 别来什么「听着 伙计」
You are knocking at my door, so don't "look, man" me.
我不是你的伙计
I'm not your man.
抱歉 先生
I'm sorry, sir.
好吧 我跟你讲个故事
All right. I'm gonna tell you a little story.
一段时间前 鲍比打给我
See, once upoin a time, Bobby called me.
叫我有这个贝拉·塔伯特的消息就联系他
Asked me to call him if I got a whiff of this Bela Talbot.
我有她消息了 就打给了他 仅此而已
I got a whiff, I called. The end.
好吧 麻烦你告诉我她在哪
Okay. If you could just tell me where she is,
那就太好了
I mean, that'd be great.
- 迪恩·温彻斯特 是吗 - 嗯
- Dean Winchester, right? - Yeah.
迪恩 我看上去像是想帮你的样子吗
Dean, do I look like I'm here to help you?
我要说不像
I'm gonna say no.
那就滚出我的地盘
Then get the hell off my property.
好吧 行吧
All right, hey, fair enough.
我还有个问题要问你
I got one more question for you, though.
我有瓶
See, I got this,
威士忌
this bottle of Scotch and…
这算是好酒吗
Is this considered good?
干杯
Well, bottoms up.
如果不是这玩意 我根本不喝
You know, I don't even bother drinking unless it's this stuff.
琼浆玉露啊
Nectar of the gods, I'm telling you.
是啊 换换口味真好
Yeah, it's a nice change, you know.
我的威士忌大都是塑料壶装的
Most of my whiskey comes from a plastic jug.
贝拉来找你是为了…
So Bela was here because…?
她想买几样东西
She wanted to buy a couple of things.
我需要点时间找齐
Which is gonna take me some time to round up.
她现在在哪
Where is she now?
小子 能问你件事吗
Kid, can I ask you something?
当然
Sure.
你还剩三周了
You got three weeks left.
你为什么要浪费时间
Why are you wasting your time,
追踪那个高傲消瘦的英国妞
chasing after that skinny, stuck-up English girl?
你怎么知道的
How do you know about that?
因为我知道事
Because I know things.
我知道很多人的很多事
I know a lot of things about a lot of people.
是吗
That so?
我知道一把玩具枪是救不了你的
I know ain't no pea shooter gonna save you.
你为什么那么肯定
What makes you so sure?
因为那是工作性质 小子
Because that's the job, kid.
即便你这次侥幸活下来
Even if you manage to scrape out of this one,
今后还会有别的
there's just gonna be something else down the road.
我们这样的人
Folks like us…
是没有幸福结局的
there ain't no happy ending.
我们都注定有那一天
We all got it coming.
你还真是乐观呢
Well, ain't you a bucket of sunshine.
我是你活下来的话 可以期待的未来
I'm what you've got to look forward to if you survive.
而且你活不下来的
Which you won't.
话说贝拉
So, Bela.
迦南旅馆
Hotel Canaan.
39号房
Room 39.
你多小心
But watch your back.
我觉得我应付得来贝拉
I think I can handle Bela.
别那么肯定
Don't be so sure about that.
你不了解她的全部
There are things that you don't know about her.
你了解吗
And you do?
对了
Right,
你知道事
because you know things.
没错
Yep.
我猜猜 你提到了她的指纹吗
And let me guess, you lift her fingerprint?
是的
Yep.
但什么都没查到
And that got you jack.
嗯
Yep.
她烧掉了指纹
She burned them off.
可能都好多年了
Probably years ago.
嗯 那你跟我们一样
Yeah, so you're right where we are.
不是
Nope.
你查过她的耳朵吗
You do her ear?
什么
Sorry?
你查过她的耳朵吗
You do her ear?
我插过她的…
Did I do her…?
伙计 我什么都愿试一次
Man, I'll try anything once,
但我不知道 那听上去不太舒服呢
but I don't know, that sounds uncomfortable.
耳朵对于人 如指纹一样独特
Ears are as unique to humans as fingerprints.
真的吗
No kidding.
当然了 这边的法庭是不认的
Course, that don't fly in the courts over here, but.
但在英国
in England?
很认这个
They're all over it.
我一个朋友的朋友的朋友
A friend of a friend of a friend…
一天内就给我传真来了10页的机密文件
faxed me 10 pages of confidential files within a day.
而我只给他寄去了一张清晰的监控截图
All I had to send him was one clean shot off the security cam.
好啊
Right.
她耳朵的清晰截图
One clean shot of her ear.
所谓的贝拉·塔伯特
The so-called Bela Talbot.
没事 我是来帮你的
It's okay, I'm here to help you.
我是来帮你的
I'm here to help you, I'm gonna help you.
好了
Okay.
天啊
God.
抱歉 好了
Sorry. I'm sorry. Okay.
好了 小心头
Okay, watch your head. Watch your head.
抱歉
Sorry.
没事了 我保证
It's gonna be fine, I promise you.
- 柯尔特枪呢 - 迪恩
- Where's the Colt? - Dean.
别说废话
No extra words.
早没了
It's long gone.
现在都在世界另一边了
Across the world by now.
你撒谎
You're lying.
我可以联系买家 会波斯语吗
I'll call the buyer. Speak Farsi?
你干什么…
What the hell are you…?
少臭美了
Don't flatter yourself.
别动
Don't move.
我说了 不在我这里
I told you, I don't have it.
嗯 我绝对相信你的话
Yeah, I'm definitely gonna take your word for it.
别动
Don't move.
已经没了
It's gone.
上飞机吧
Get on a plane if you must.
找到那买家 你或许最终能追上他
Track down the buyer. You might catch up to him, eventually.
你要杀了我吗
Are you going to kill me?
对
Yeah.
你不是冷血的人
You're not the cold-blooded type.
像你那样冷血吗
You mean, like you?
是啊
It's true.
我无法想象杀我的父母
See, I couldn't imagine killing my parents.
- 我不知道你说… - 你知道
- I don't know what you're talk… - Yes, you do.
你当时多大 14岁吗
You were, what, 14?
你父母死于可疑车祸
Your folks die in some shady car accident,
警方怀疑刹车线被剪
police suspected a slashed brake line…
但烧得无法分辨了
but it was all too crispy to tell.
而小贝拉呢
Cut to little Bela…
抱歉
I'm sorry.
是阿比
Abbie.
继承了百万
Inheriting millions.
- 你怎么知… - 不重要
- How did you even…? - Doesn't matter.
他们是好人
They were lovely people.
而我杀了他们
And I killed them.
并因此有钱了
And I got rich.
我完全不在乎
I can't be bothered to give a damn.
就像我也不在乎你的死活
Just like I don't care what happens to you.
你让我恶心
You make me sick.
彼此彼此
Likewise.
你不值得
You're not worth it.
（伊利旅馆）
成功了
It worked.
他找到我了
He found me.
不 萨姆没一起来
No, Sam wasn't with him.
但我知道他们在哪
But I know where they are.
- 迪恩 - 嗯
- Dean? - Yeah.
你找到柯尔特枪了吗
Did you get the Colt?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
- 那贝拉… - 不不
- So does that mean Bela is, uh…? - No, no.
她该死十几遍 但我做不到
She deserves to die a dozen times over, but I couldn't do it.
- 迪恩 - 我真完蛋了 萨姆
- Dean… - I'm really screwed, Sammy.
- 不 你… - 你是对的
- No, you're just… - Look, you were right,
找贝拉是白费功夫
you know, Bela was a goose chase.
柯尔特枪丢了
The CoIt's gone.
我这次真完蛋了 萨姆
And this time I'm really screwed, Sam.
或许还没有
Maybe not.
迪恩 我找到了班顿的小屋
Dean, I found Benton's cabin.
- 你没事吧 他在那里吗 - 嗯
- You okay? Was he there? - Yeah.
- 你杀掉他了吗 - 没有
- Did you kill him? - No.
- 什么叫没有 - 迪恩 拜托
- What do you mean, no? - Dean, please.
听我说
Just listen for a second.
我找到了他的实验笔记 上面有秘方
I found his lab book and it has the formula.
- 什么 永生秘方吗 - 对
- What, the live-forever formula? - Yeah.
好啊 我猜猜 我要拿婴儿头骨喝血吗
Great, let me guess, I gotta drink blood out of a baby's skull?
不 问题就在这里 这不是黑魔法
No, that's the thing, it's not black magic.
并没有血祭什么的
There's no blood sacrifice or anything.
只是科学 迪恩
It's just science, Dean.
非常奇怪的科学 但是
Very, very, extremely weird science, but…
等等 你说什么呢
Wait, wait, what are you saying?
- 你觉得… - 迪恩 我觉得或许可行
- You think…? - Dean, I think it might be doable.
我知道我们遭遇了很多挫折
I mean, I know we've hit a lot of walls,
但我觉得这个秘方 可能是解决之道
but I mean, I think this formula, I think it might be it.
这或许能救你
This could save you.
好吧 这个秘方
Okay, so this formula…
我们还没安全呢
Well, I mean, look, we're not in the clear yet,
还有些地方我不懂
there are still things that I don't get…
萨姆
Sam?
Sammy?
放松吧
You can relax.
会没事的
It's all gonna be okay.
你不需要担心
Ain't nothing gonna happen here.
要发生的事 萨姆
that you got to worry about, Sammy.
你从手术中活下来的几率
And your chances of coming out of this procedure alive…
是很大的
very, very high.
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?
我知道
I know.
你觉得我是个怪物 是吧
You think I'm some kind of monster, don't you? Well,
我得告诉你
I gotta tell you,
我从未做过什么我不非得做的事
I have never done one thing that I did not have to do.
永生什么的 损耗很高
This whole eternal life thing is very high-maintenance.
有什么坏掉了 比如我的眼睛
Something goes bad, like my eyes here,
就得拿新的换
you gotta replace them.
有时 有些东西被损坏
And sometimes, things get damaged,
比如当你父亲挖出我的心脏
like when your father cut out my heart.
那
Now, that…
就特别不方便
That was very inconvenient.
你肯定能想象 我在他的日记里
So I'm sure that you can understand all the joy I felt,
读到自己时 心情多愉快
when I read all about myself here in his journal.
让这整件事
Kind of makes this whole thing…
感觉像种家庭团聚 是吧
just feel like some kind of family reunion, don't it?
那么我们现在该开始了
Well, I guess it's about time that we get this thing started.
随你开枪吧
Shoot all you want.
刀吗
A knife?
永生你是哪里不明白了
What part of immortality do you not understand?
心脏可惜了
Pity about the heart, though.
还是新的呢
It was a brand-new one.
很好
Good.
应该泵得很有力
Should be pumping nice and strong.
把这玩意送遍你全身
Sending this stuff throughout your whole body.
（氯仿）
我在楼上拿了一瓶
See, I picked up your little bottle upstairs.
然后在刀上沾了点
and dipped the knife in it.
好啊 医生
Hiya, Doc.
醒来啦 吃早餐啦
Wakey wakey eggs and bakey.
- 求你 - 求什么
- Please. - Please what?
你杀人杀了150多年了
You've been killing poor bastards for over 150 years.
现在还要提要求
and now you got a request?
闭嘴吧
Shut up.
你不懂 我可以帮你
You don't understand, I can help you.
我知道你需要什么
I know what you need.
我要把他切成小块
I'm gonna have to cut him open into litlle bits.
这永生什么的真麻烦
You know, this immortality thing is a bitch.
我能帮你解读秘方
I can read the formula for you.
永生
You know, immortality…
永远年轻 永远不死
forever young, never die.
迪恩
Dean.
萨姆
Sam.
怎么了
What?
要么是三周后下地狱
I mean, we're talking hell in three weeks.
要么是半个世纪后需要换个胰脏
or needing a new pancreas in what, half a century.
是啊 那玩意可不是便利店就有
Yeah. Well, you can't exactly get those at a Kwik-E-Mart.
这是不完美
It's not perfect,
但能给我们争取时间 想更好的办法
but it buys us more time to think of something better.
我们就是需要时间 迪恩 求你
We just need time, Dean. I mean, please, just…
考虑一下吧
just think about it.
不
No.
迪恩 你不想活吗
Dean, don't you wanna live?
他那不叫活
What he is isn't living.
- 这很简单 - 简单
- Look, this is simple. - Simple?
对我来说就是很简单 黑白分明 人怪分明
To me it is, okay? Black or white. Human, not human.
医生
You see, what the doc is…
他是个怪物
He's a freaking monster.
我不能那么做
I can't do it.
我宁可下地狱
I would rather go to hell.
你不懂 我可以帮你
You don't understand. I can help you.
我要解决了他
Now, I'm gonna take care of him.
你帮不帮我自己决定
You can either help me or not. It's up to you.
不 别犯傻了
No, no. Don't be stupid!
我可以帮你 别
I can help you. No.
- 在里面享受永生吧 医生 - 我可以救你
- Enjoy forever in there, Doc. - I can save you.
放我出去
Let me out!
Let me out.
我可以救你
I can save you!
不 别
No, don't! Don't!
不 放我出去
No, let me out, let me out.
放我出去 放我出去
Let me out, let me out, let me out.
不
No!
（伊利旅馆）
好啊 贝拉
Hiya, Bela.
有件事你可能不知道
Here's a fun fact you may not know.
我偷走旅馆收据时 我感到你手摸我兜了
I felt your hand in my pocket when you swiped that motel receipt.
你不懂
You don't understand.
我想我很清楚是怎么回事
I'm pretty sure I understand perfectly.
我在你的旅馆房间里注意到了一件有趣的东西
You see, I noticed something interesting in your hotel room.
就掖在门上方
Something tucked above the door.
一种植物
An herb.
荚莲树皮
Devil's shoestring?
那玩意只有一种用途
Well, there's only one use for that.
抵御地狱之犬
Holding Hellhounds at bay.
所以你知道我做了什么吗
So you know what I did?
我回去又看了一遍你父母的讣告
I went back and I took another look at your folks' obit.
原来 他们是十年前的今天死的
Turns out, they died 10 years ago today.
你没杀他们
You didn't kill them.
是一个恶魔替你下的手
A demon did your dirty work.
你做了交易 是吧 贝拉
You made a deal, didn't you, Bela?
收债的日子要到了
And it's come due.
我可以替你解决他们
I can take care of them for you.
你也不用付出什么
And it won't even cost you anything…
十年里都不用
for 10 whole years.
所以你才偷走了柯尔特枪吗
So is that why you stole the Colt?
想摆脱你的交易
Try to wiggle out of your deal?
我们的枪换你的灵魂
Our gun for your soul?
是的
Yes.
但我猜偷柯尔特枪还不够 是吧
But stealing the Colt wasn't quite enough, I'm guessing.
他们改变了交易
They changed the deal.
他们要我杀了萨姆
They wanted me to kill Sam.
真的吗
Really?
恶魔这么不守信用
Demons untrustworthy.
震惊了
Shocker.
截止日期快到了呢
That's, uh, kind of a tight deadline too.
几点了
What time is it?
看啊 马上午夜了
Look at that, almost midnight.
迪恩 我需要帮助
Dean, listen, I need help.
亲爱的 那早来不及了
Sweetheart, we are weeks past help.
我知道我不配
I know I don't deserve it.
知道吗 你说对了 你不配
You know what, you're right, you don't.
但知道最可惜的是什么吗
But you know what the bitch of the bunch is?
如果你肯早点来找我们求助
If you would've just come to us sooner and asked for help…
我们或许还能拿柯尔特枪救你
we probably could've taken the Colt and saved you.
我知道 也救你自己
I know, and saved yourself.
我知道你的交易 迪恩
I know about your deal, Dean.
谁告诉你的
And who told you that?
掌握合约的那个恶魔
The demon that holds it.
她也掌握了我的合约
She holds mine too.
她说她掌握着所有的合约
She says she holds every deal.
- 她吗 - 她叫莉莉丝
- She? - Her name's Lilith.
莉莉丝吗
Lilith?
我为什么要信你
Why should I believe you?
没有理由 但这是真的
You shouldn't, but it's the truth.
这帮不了你 贝拉
This can't help you, Bela.
现在太迟了 你为什么要告诉我
Not now. Why are you telling me this?
因为你或许能杀了那贱人
Because just maybe you can kill the bitch.
地狱见了
I'll see you in hell.